question_data = [
    # {"text": "A slug's blood is green.", "answer": "True"},
    # {"text": "The loudest animal is the African Elephant.", "answer": "False"},
    # {"text": "Approximately one quarter of human bones are in the feet.", "answer": "True"},
    # {"text": "The total surface area of a human lungs is the size of a football pitch.", "answer": "True"},
    # {"text": "In West Virginia, USA, if you accidentally hit an animal with your car, you are free to take it home to"
    #          " eat.", "answer": "True"},
    # {"text": "In London, UK, if you happen to die in the House of Parliament, you are entitled to a state"
    #          " funeral.", "answer": "False"},
    # {"text": "It is illegal to pee in the Ocean in Portugal.", "answer": "True"},
    # {"text": "You can lead a cow down stairs but not up stairs.", "answer": "False"},
    # {"text": "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.", "answer": "True"},
    # {"text": "Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was 'Moon'.", "answer": "True"},
    # {"text": "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times.", "answer": "False"},
    # {"text": "A few ounces of chocolate can to kill a small dog.", "answer": "True"}


    # ABAIXO VEM QUESTÃ•ES DE OUTRA FONTE DE DADOS (opentdb.com) PARA DEMONSTRAR A MODULARIDADE DA POO


    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The US emergency hotline is 911 because of the September 11th terrorist attacks.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Scottish producer Calvin Harris is from the town of Dumfries, Scotland.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Studio Ghibli is a Japanese animation studio responsible for the films"
                 " 'Wolf Children' and 'The Boy and the Beast'.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In 2016, the IUCN reclassified the status of Giant Pandas from endangered to vulnerable.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The 2005 video game 'Call of Duty 2: Big Red One' is not available on PC.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "TF2: Sentry rocket damage falloff is calculated based on the distance between the"
                 " sentry and the enemy, not the engineer and the enemy",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The name of the attack 'Kamehameha' in Dragon Ball Z was named after a"
                 " famous king of Hawaii.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In 'JoJo&#039;s Bizarre Adventure', Father Enrico Pucchi uses a total of"
                 " 3 stands in Part 6: Stone Ocean.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Board Games", "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "'Rich Uncle Pennybags' from the board game 'Monopoly' wears a monocle.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "Pete Townshend&#039;s solo album, 'White City: A Novel', is set in"
                 " the metropolitan area of Chicago.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Nova Scotia is on the east coast of Canada.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Rabbits are carnivores.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
